ballcharts.com 2018-05-14

# BALLCHARTS - Privacy

BallCharts.com recognizes that privacy is extremely important. This Privacy Policy applies to all web sites and products offered by BallCharts.com. The majority of BallCharts.com's websites are intended for a general audience and this policy describes our general use of information. For BallCharts.com's websites that may be used by a younger audience, more specific policies applicable to children under the age of 13 will be located on each such site. View the BallCharts.com Children's Privacy Policy.

### BallCharts.com Privacy Policy

We collect information volunteered by site visitors and members as well as aggregate information about what pages are visited. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service. With the exception of the cases indicated below, the information we collect is not shared with or sold to other organizations for any purpose, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission. We will share collected information if it is required to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 

### Information Gathered and Usage

When you create a web site or signup for a BallCharts.com account or other BallCharts.com service that requires registration, we may ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, such as our upgraded web site services, we also request credit card or other payment account information. 

BallCharts.com uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

### Cookies

When you visit BallCharts.com, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer or other device to uniquely identify your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing preferences and tracking usage trends. 

BallCharts.com also uses cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web. We may set one or more cookies in your browser when you visit a website, including BallCharts.com sites that use our advertising cookies, and view or click on an ad supported by BallCharts.com’s advertising services. 

Cookies are required to use some features of BallCharts.com. We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. 

### Data Storage

Although BallCharts.com owns the code, databases, and all rights to the BallCharts.com website, you retain all rights to your data.

BallCharts.com uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run this site.

### Disclosure

BallCharts.com may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service. 

### Changes

BallCharts.com may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your BallCharts.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

### Questions

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
